Guide to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association records, circa 1800-2022 MS2027
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administration files, 1828-2010; MS2027 Series 2
  - Public relations files: Map, The Patowmack Canal-Great Falls Park, VA, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Public relations files: Map, Delaware & Lehigh Navigation Canal-PA, Circa 1990 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Public relations files: Map, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Public relations files: Map, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal-Facilities Guide, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Public relations files: Map, Cumberland Terminus, MD, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Public relations files: Map, Department of Interior-Great Falls Park, VA, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Public relations files: Map, Department of Interior-Volunteers in Parks, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Public relations files: Map, Four Locks, MD, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Public relations files: Map, Great Falls Tavern, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Public relations files: Map, Harpers Ferry, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Public relations files: Map, National Trails System, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Public relations files: Map, Paw Paw Tunnel, MD, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Public relations files: Map, Cuyahoga Valley, OH, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Public relations files: Map, Delaware & Raritan Canal State Park, Circa 1992 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Public relations files: Map, Photocopy of 1855 Washington DC canals, nd, undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Public relations files: Map, Antietam Creek-Shepersdown Historic Trail, nd, undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Public relations files: Map, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal-Locks 37 to Washington, nd, undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Public relations files: Map, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal-150 to 170 miles from Georgetown, nd, undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Public relations files: Map, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal-Miles 173.37 to 184.50, nd, undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Public relations files: Map, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal-North Branch to Hillsborn, undated (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Public relations files: Map, Flyer-Exhibit, "Moving Maryland-350 Years of Transportation", nd, undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Public relations files: Map, Georgetown Development Activity Map, nd, undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Public relations files: Map, Harpers Ferry-Canal Improvements-Alternatives, nd, undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Public relations files: Map, Proposed Improvements-Potomac River Shoreline Between Washington Canoe Club & Alexandria Aqueduct, nd, undated (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Public relations files: Map, Whitehurst Freeway Corridor Study, nd, undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Public relations files: Press Release, River Bend Dam Opposition, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Public relations files: Press Release, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Public relations files: Press Release, The Magnificent Ditch-Film Preservation, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Public relations files: Press Releases, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Public relations files: Press Releases, National Park Service, 1970-1992 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Public relations files: Correspondence, Description of photographs from 1954 Heritage Hike, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Public relations files: Correspondence, Recording of Joe Sandbower, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Public relations files: Film Script, "Allegheny Portage Railroad", 1992 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Public relations files: Order Form, Towpath Guide-Seneca to Harpers Ferry, nd, undated (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, from the Washington Intelligencer, 1850 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, "Hermit of Great Falls Thinks 1889 Potomac Flood was best,", 1936 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, "Low-Cost Wilderness Trips,", 1939 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Proposed As Recreation Park,", 1953 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Clipping: "Potomac Parkway", 1954 January 03; Item 1
    - Clipping: "Potomac Sanctuary", 1954 January 19; Item 2
    - Clipping: "We Accept", 1954 January 21; Item 3
    - Clippings: "Douglas Band Heads Out for Canal Hike" and "Canal Hike", 1954 March 20-22; Item 4
    - Clipping: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal: A Report", 1964 March 31; Item 5
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Clipping: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Park Bill Is Urged", 1957 June 13; Item 1
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, "A Canal to open the West,", 1965 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Clipping: "Byron Favors Chesapeake & Ohio Canal as Retreat", 1968 August 29; Item 1
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings about flood damage, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal to be Dedicated to Justice Douglas", 1977 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, "A Point of Rocks Cruise,", 1985 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, "Under Sail Along Ontario's Rideau,", 1992 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, September/10/1992 issue of "Leaves" with article entitled, "An Historical Account," (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park and flood damage, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park, nd, undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, oversized clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association National Park, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, oversized clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association National Park, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, oversized clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association National Park, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, oversized clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association National Park, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, oversized clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association National Park, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, oversized clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association National Park, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, oversized clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association National Park, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, oversized clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association National Park, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, oversized clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association National Park, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, oversized clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association National Park, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, oversized clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association National Park, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, oversized clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association National Park, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, oversized clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association National Park, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, oversized clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association National Park, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, "County Council Votes to Purchase Rail line,", 1988 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, "Canal Parkway vs. Airport Boulevard,", 1989 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, "Take One Abandoned Canal, add water,", 1991 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, oversized clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association National Park, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, oversized clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association National Park, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, oversized clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association National Park, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, oversized clippings related to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association National Park, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Public relations files: Articles and Clippings, "Presidential Participation in Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Cleanup heavy with Symbolism,", 1996 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Public relations files: Memorabilia: T-Shirt, Green and yellow "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association" shirt with logo, nd, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Public relations files: Memorabilia: Name Tag, Green and white "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association -- 10th Reunion Hike" tags (3), 1964 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Public relations files: Memorabilia: Pin, Gold and black "National Park Service -- 50th Anniversary -- 1916-1966". Includes name of "Mr. (Colin) Ritter" (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Public relations files: Memorabilia: Patches, Green and yellow "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association -- Justice Douglas Reunion Hike -- 04/16-29/1989" (3) (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Public relations files: Memorabilia: Patches, Green and yellow "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association" with barge logo (3), nd, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Public relations files: Memorabilia: Patches, Green and yellow "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association" with barge logo (3) felt, nd, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Public relations files: Memorabilia: Pins, Green and yellow, "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association -- Reunion Hike" name tags, nd, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Public relations files: Exhibit Panels, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal- "Great Falls Tavern", nd, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Public relations files: Exhibit Panels, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal- "David Humphrey 1785 letter to Geo. Washington", nd, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Public relations files: Exhibit Panels, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal- "Built between 1828 & 1850", nd, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Public relations files: Exhibit Panels, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal- "In the peak year of 1851", nd, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Public relations files: Exhibit Panels, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal- "Widewater", nd, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Public relations files: Exhibit Panels, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal- "Notice! Georgetown level regulations", nd, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Public relations files: Exhibit Panels, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal-Map of Chesapeake & Ohio Co., History of Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Co., History of Chesapeake & Ohio Canal, Building the canal, The canal water system", nd, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Public relations files: Exhibit Panels, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal-Round Trip Cement Mill, Steam Pump, nd, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Public relations files: Exhibit Panels, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal-Four Lock, Lock 33, A lift lock, Dam 4-Winch House, nd, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Public relations files: Exhibit Panels, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal-Whites Ferry, Ohio Canal boat, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal boat design, nd, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Public relations files: Exhibit Panels, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal-Monocacy Aqueduct, Conocoleague Aqueduct, nd, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Public relations files: Exhibit Panels, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal-Paw Paw Tunnel, nd, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Public relations files: Invitations, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Railroad Lift Bridge, 1991 September 12 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Public relations files: Maps, Frederick Co., MD, Mid-Atlantic Region trails, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal near Wiley Ford Bridge, 1873-1991 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Public relations files: Blueprint, Baltimore & Ohio Railroad Co. System-Pres. Passenger Station, 1919 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Public relations files: Blueprint, Baltimore & Ohio Railroad Co. System-Pres. Passenger Station-Alterations, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Public relations files: Map, Allegeny Co., MD-Topographic map, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Public relations: Thru hike publicity, 1999; Series 2 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Program files: Event, Announcement for "Save the Carousel at Glen Echo Park", 1970 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Program files: Event, Itinerary, "Potomac River Trip", 1975 August (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Program files: Event, Announcement for "Fortification History Hike", 1976 March (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Program files: Event, Correspondence, Capital Crescent Trail -- Groundbreaking, 1993 June 03 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Program files: Event, Program, National Capital Region/National Park Service -- Partnership-Leadership-Reception and Awards Ceremony, 1994 June 06 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Program files: Event, Program, Civil War Series, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Program files: Event, Announcement for Station Square Project-Groundbreaking, 06/02, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Program files: Event, Announcement for George Washington's Boatmen, 06/30, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Program files: Volunteer files: Meeting, Association Luncheon, 1969 November 22 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Program files: Volunteer files: Subject Files, Gypsy Moth Project, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Program files: Volunteer files: Report, Vegetation Control, 1983 March (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Program files: Volunteer files: Correspondence, 1983-1991 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Program files: Volunteer files: Amendment, Volunteers in the Park Act, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Program files: Volunteer files: Report, VIP Towpath comments, 1989 January (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Program files: Volunteer files: Notes, Youth Conservation Program, nd, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Program files: Volunteer files: Fact Sheet, Volunteers in Parks, nd, undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Program files: Volunteer files: List, Palisades District project, nd, undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Program files: Volunteer files: List, Piedmont District project, nd, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Program files: Volunteer files: List, Allegheny District project, nd, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Correspondence, Carl Linden, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Correspondence, Russ Dickerman to John Chandler, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Correspondence, Tom Hahn, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Correspondence, Bruce Wood, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Correspondence, Bruce Wood, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Correspondence, Grant Conway, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Correspondence, Richard Stanton to Harold Larsen, 1981-1988 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Correspondence, Karen Gray, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Directories, 1972-1991 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Guidelines, 1975-1990 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: List, Canal Sections, nd, undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Meeting, Minutes, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Memorandum, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Memorandum, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Memorandum, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Memorandum, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Memorandum, nd, undated (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Newsletter, The Level Walker, Vol. 1-2, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Questionnaire, People's Plan for a Park, Circa 1972 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Report, Towpath, 1970-1975 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Report, "Resume of Level Walkers Answers to the Questionnaire Regarding the Development of Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Park", Circa 1973 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Reports, Towpath-Section 44 -- Harold and Jane Larson, 1975-1995 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Reports, Towpath, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Reports, Level 19, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Reports, Towpath-incomplete, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Reports, Towpath, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Reports, Towpath, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Reports, Towpath, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Program files: Level Walkers Program: Reports, Short Form, nd, undated (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Program files: Heritage Hike files: Correspondence, Colin Ritter, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Program files: Heritage Hike files: Correspondence, Anthony Smith, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Program files: Heritage Hike files: Correspondence, Jack Durham, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Program files: Heritage Hike files: Correspondence, Bruce Wood, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Program files: Heritage Hike files: Correspondence, 22nd Hike, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Program files: Heritage Hike files: Correspondence, John Chandler, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Program files: Heritage Hike files: Correspondence, 29th Hike, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Program files: Heritage Hike files: Correspondence, Hotel arrangements, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Program files: Heritage Hike files: Correspondence, John Chandler, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Program files: Heritage Hike files: Correspondence, Bruce Wood, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Program files: Heritage Hike files: Correspondence, Richard Stanton, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Program files: Heritage Hike files: Correspondence, Fall Picnic, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Program files: Heritage Hike files: Correspondence, Registration deposits, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Program files: Heritage Hike files: Correspondence, Brunswick Campsite donation, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Program files: Heritage Hike files: Correspondence, Richard Stanton, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Program files: Heritage Hike files: Correspondence, Camping permit, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 16)